Imagine being a child awakened in the middle of the night
by a Blackhawk helicopter landing on your roof.
Kids in Chicago are getting hit by strays.
If they see a Blackhawk land on a roof to round up bad guys,
that's a dream come true.
Ribs never worried about the children before.
He thinks ice is a bigger threat than street gangs.
The whole city's infested.
We learned that the Chicago city streets
have 110,000 gang members.
That's right, you heard me right.
They had 1,200 shootings this year alone, 360 homicides.
Parts of Chicago are more dangerous than Afghanistan.
5% of the people in Chicago are gang members.
Almost 10% of the city is illegal.
So the guard's going in.
Over 500 members of the guard from Illinois, Texas,
and California have been deployed for a 60-day mission.
And what's J.B. Beck actually going to do about it?
Nothing.
If he tells Chicago PD to block the guard,
you think the police are loyal to Ribs or the president?